<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <id>urn:uuid:ED89B8FA-0E0B-46CC-A90B-595E69AE9A7E</id>
  <title>Ark Server Manager Version Feed</title>
  <subtitle>This is the Ark Server Manager release version feed.</subtitle>
  <link href="http://servermanagers.freeforums.net/" />
  <updated>2018-05-01T00:00:00Z</updated>

  <entry>
    <id>urn:uuid:0B85C4D7-991C-4954-9B39-E30146B8CA33</id>
    <title>1.0.323 (1.0.323.19)</title>
    <summary>1.0.323.19</summary>
    <link href="http://arkservermanager.freeforums.net/thread/5103/1-323-test-build" />
    <updated>2017-09-01T11:30:00Z</updated>
    <content type="xhtml">
      <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
        <p>
          <u>BUGFIX</u><br/>
          <ul>
            <li>This version fixes a few duplicate shutdown messages introduced with the Always Show Shutdown Reason in last release (322).</li>
          </ul>
          <u>NEW</u><br/>
          <ul>
            <li>Version Details Window - a new window to show the version updates.</li>
            <li>This version adds a very basic Player List. This player list is only available when RCON is disabled, replaces the RCON button with a Players button.<br/><br/>
            The player list only reads the ARK player and tribe files and displays them in a list. Without RCON I am unable to determine which player is online, so Online status is never shown here.<br/><br/>
            Right-click on a player to get a few options.<br/><br/>
            This list is only designed to give server owners WITHOUT RCON, the ability to see who is connecting to their server.</li>
            <li>This version adds a global setting to shutdown or keep open the Server Shutdown window after it is finished - used for testing.</li>
            <li>Gamedata storage changes</li>
          </ul>
          <u>CHANGE</u><br/>
          <ul>
            <li>Completely re-written the RCON player profile load.<br/>
            It should now only call the update one at a time - should remove the ListPlayers spam.<br/>
            It should not freeze ASM when the profiles are now loading.</li>
            <li>This version updates the French translation file.</li>
            <li>The auto-update now has a file copy failure retry. If the file fails to copy, it will try 3 times with a 5 second delay in between.</li>
            <li>The Server Files section is now read-only when the server is running.</li>
            <li>The Server Files section is now an option in the Profile Sync.</li>
            <li>The Shutdown window will now always open regardless of if RCON is enabled/disabled.</li>
            <li>Added Server, Query and RCON port validation to the profile validation. Valid range is 0 - 65535.</li>
            <li>This version adds the .arktributetribe files to the backup and restore functions.</li>
            <li>A confirmation dialog has been added when using the Write Timestamp button in the Mod Details window.</li>
            <li>The ArkApplication filter comboboxes have been changed, so that the display values can be globalized.</li>
          </ul>
        </p>
      </div>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>bletch</name>
      <email>bletch1971@hotmail.com</email>
    </author>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <id>urn:uuid:C5C0521B-3CE8-4DA7-BE03-B57378A78966</id>
    <title>1.0.322 (1.0.322.7)</title>
    <summary>1.0.322.7</summary>
    <link href="http://arkservermanager.freeforums.net/thread/3/downloads" />
    <updated>2018-04-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <content type="xhtml">
      <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
        <p>
          <u>NEW</u>
          <ul>
            <li>Mod Details Window - A new 'Timestamp' column has been added to shows the timestamp of the last time the mod was updated. This value is returned from the steam servers.</li>
            <li>Mod Details Window - A new button has been added to each row. This button will allow you to manually set the value in the LastUpdatedASM.txt files. This should only be used if you MUST update a mod by manually copying the files.</li>
            <li>Shutdown Reason Broadcast - A new option has been added to the global settings, that will broadcast the shutdown reason with every shutdown message. If disabled, the shutdown reason is only broadcast at the start of the shutdown.</li>
          </ul>
        </p>
      </div>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>bletch</name>
      <email>bletch1971@hotmail.com</email>
    </author>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <id>urn:uuid:81419AF8-3047-456D-B94E-74BEC336D660</id>
    <title>1.0.321 (1.0.321.2)</title>
    <summary>1.0.321.2</summary>
    <link href="http://arkservermanager.freeforums.net/thread/3/downloads" />
    <updated>2018-04-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <content type="xhtml">
      <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
        <p>
          <u>NEW</u>
          <ul>
            <li>Added Aberrant Direbear and Bigfoot versions. (thanks @spikeydragoon)</li>
            <li>Updated Ban Url.</li>
          </ul>
          <u>CHANGED</u>
          <ul>
            <li>RU Translation file updated. (thanks @varlonec)</li>
            <li>FR Translation file updated. (thanks @angemymy)</li>
          </ul>
        </p>
      </div>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>bletch</name>
      <email>bletch1971@hotmail.com</email>
    </author>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <id>urn:uuid:CCE2F68C-3F1C-45F7-A234-34F09C892402</id>
    <title>1.0.320 (1.0.320.8)</title>
    <summary>1.0.320.8</summary>
    <link href="http://arkservermanager.freeforums.net/thread/3/downloads" />
    <updated>2018-04-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <content type="xhtml">
      <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
        <p>
          <u>NEW</u>
          <ul>
            <li>FR Translation file added. (thanks @angemymy)</li>
          </ul>
          <u>CHANGED</u>
          <ul>
            <li>RU Translation file updated. (thanks @varlonec)</li>
            <li>CN Translation file updated. (thanks @acme)</li>
            <li>
              <font color="#1979e6">ARK 278.0 options added.</font><br/>
              ServerAllowAnsel -> Administration section<br/>
              AllowHideDamageSourceFromLogs -> Administration section<br/>
              TribeNameChangeCooldown -> Rules section<br/>
              RandomSupplyCratePoints -> Rules section<br/>
              DisableWeatherFog -> Environment section<br/>
              bHardLimitTurretsInRange -> Structures section<br/>
              TamedDinoCharacterFoodDrainMultiplier -> Dino section<br/>
              TamedDinoTorporDrainMultiplier -> Dino section<br/>
              WildDinoCharacterFoodDrainMultiplier -> Dino section<br/>
              WildDinoTorporDrainMultiplier -> Dino section<br/>
              PassiveTameIntervalMultiplier -> Dino section<br/>
              PreventOfflinePvPConnectionInvincibleInterval -> Rules section<br/>
            </li>
          </ul>
        </p>
      </div>
    </content>
    <author>
      <name>bletch</name>
      <email>bletch1971@hotmail.com</email>
    </author>
  </entry>

</feed>
